# **Michael Chang**

Game Developer & Designer Multimedia Artist Based in Los Angeles, California Full Stack developer specializing in game with over 8+ years of experience in both designing and developing games. I also do web development and graphic design. Animation and illustration work is mostly a hobby, but I am available for freelancing in that field. Knowledgeable in video game marketing and computer hardware.

Portfolio: https://mchang0004.github.io/portfolio/

Itch.io: https://mchang0004.itch.io/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-chang-62b89a203/ Email: mchang0004@gmail.com

## Education

**Loyola Marymount University** 

B.A. - Multimedia Arts Minor - Computer Science August 2020 - May 2024

The Cambridge Tradition

Creative Writing & Computer Science July 2018 - August 2018

# Skills

#### **Coding Languages:**

- C/C++
- HTML/CSS/JS

#### Applications:

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Arduino IDE
- <u>Blender</u>
- OBS/Streamlabs
- Unity
- Unreal Engine

# Interests

Animation and Illustration Table Top Games Photography Creative Writing



# **Work Experience**

#### Cool Vibes Esports | 2019 - Current | Remote

- -Team Manager & Event Coordinator
- ·Handles member entry and game competition events

#### Novalight Games | Jan - May 2024 | Remote

- Internship, worked on Unity games
- -QA testing and worked on character/player interaction
- Designing inventory system

#### EGD Collective | June - August 2021 | Remote

- Internship and Creative Team
- -At EGD, I taught course on Table Top RPG Design. Multiple presentations on breaking down mechanics and teaching new players.
- -Also worked on the creative team to create website designs and stream overlays/graphics.

### Target | July - August 2022 | Los Angeles, California

-General Merchandise Expert

#### Barn 2 Robotics | 2016 - 2020 | Portola Valley, California

-Component Engineering, Collaboration and Communication skills while working with robotics and CAD modeling.

# **Projects**

- **KAF | Unity | Solo Project**•KAF immerses the player in a dream world where they must complete objectives to wake up.
- ·The game was shown in an exhibition.
- ·Available on Itch.io

# Artifacts of Sorellia | Unity | Solo Project Artifacts of Sorellia is a FPS rogue-like card collection game. The

- game revolves around collecting artifacts to purchase cards.
- ·This game was created in 8 weeks for a Unity Development Class
- ·Demo available on Itch.io

#### Stars of Sorellia | Unity | Solo Project

·Stars of Sorellia is an ongoing Unity 2D RPG game. The game is currently in alpha stages. I'm currently working on the developing mechanics and world building. Demo available on Itch.io

### Forest Adventure | Custom Javascript Engine

•Forest Adventure is a turn-based RPG that works in browser.